ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Two Guys (From Harrison), 1977 (Box 83, Folder 65)
- U.S. Padding Corp., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 66)
- Unarco Industries, Inc. (Federal Stainless Sink), 1972 (Box 83, Folder 67)
- Uniform Pants Company, Inc., 1960 (Box 83, Folder 68)
- Union Asbestos & Rubber Co., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 69)
- Union Bridge Manufacturing Corp., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 70)
- Union Carbide Corp., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 71)
- Union Company, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 72)
- Union Shirt Co., Inc., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 73)
- Union Textile Printers, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 74)
- Union Wadding Company, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 75)
- Unique Leather, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 76)
- United Bag Co., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 77)
- United Carpet, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 78)
- United Factors, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 79)
- United Garment Manufacturing Co., 1964 (Box 83, Folder 80)
- United International (United Merchants & Manufacturers), 1974 (Box 83, Folder 81)
- United Manufacturing, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 82)
- United Merchant & Manufacturers (Robert Hall), 1977 (Box 83, Folder 83)
- United Steel Products, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 84)
- Universal Needle Craft, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 85)
- Universal Shirt Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 86)
- Universal Southern Label Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 87)
- Universal Sportswear Company, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 88)
- V & M Garment Co., 1966 (Box 83, Folder 89)
- V.T.M. Finishing Co., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 90)
- Val D'Or Industries, Inc., 1974 (Box 83, Folder 91)
- Valmy Garment Company, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 92)
- Vanderbilt, Gloria for Murjani, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 93)
- Van Guard Carpet Mills, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 94)
- Van Raalte Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 95)
- Vanguard Manufacturing, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 96)
- Venice Industries, Inc., 1975 (Box 83, Folder 97)
- Verve Shirt Company, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 98)
- Victor Knitting Mills, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 99)
- Virginia Chemicals, Inc. (Virchem of Canada, Inc.), 1978 (Box 83, Folder 100)
- Voltex, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 101)
- Volume Shoe Corporation, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 102)
- W. W. Jewelers, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 103)
- Waldo Shoe Corp., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 104)
- Wallachs, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 105)
- Wagner Forming Fabrics, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 106)
- Warwick USA, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 107)
- Washington Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 108)
- Waters, D. F. & Son, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 109)
- Watlow Electric Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 110)
- Watlow Winona, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 111)
- Waverly Mills, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 112)
- Weitz, John Contour Clothes, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 113)
- Weitz, S. & Co., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 114)
- Well Made Pants Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 115)
- Wells & Coverly, Inc., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 116)
- Wells, Marshall, Corp., 1968 (Box 83, Folder 117)
- Wells National Services Corp., 1973 (Box 83, Folder 118)
- Wells & Wade Corp., 1968 (Box 83, Folder 119)
- Welsh Allyn, Inc., 1974 (Box 83, Folder 120)
- Werner-Hilton, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 121)
- West End International, Inc., 1973 (Box 83, Folder 122)
- West Knitting Corp., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 123)
- West Virginia Garment Co., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 124)
- Western Foam Pak, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 125)
- Western State Bank, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 126)
- Western Textile Mills, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 127)
- Westforth Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 128)
- Westwood, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 129)
- Westwood Pharmaceuticals, Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 130)
- Wex-Tex of Dothan, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 131)
- Whitaker, Fred, Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 132)
- White Automotive Corp., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 133)
- White Consolidated Industries, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 134)
- Whiteville Apparel Corp., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 135)
- Whittaker Corporation (Textiles Service Center), 1973 (Box 83, Folder 136)
- Whittaker Knitting Mills, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 137)
- Whittier Mills Company, Inc., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 138)
- Widder Bros., Inc., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 139)
- Wide Awake Shirt Company, Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 140)
- Wilcox Garment Company, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 141)
- Willette Corp. of New Jersey, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 142)
- Willow Glen Sportswear, Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 143)
- Wilson & Company, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 144)
- Wilson Enterprise, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 145)
- Wilson Manufacturing Company, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 146)
- Wimbledon Fashions, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 147)
- Wincraft, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 148)
- Winchester Sportswear, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 149)
- Wincomo Dyeing & Finishing Corp, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 150)
- Windbreaker, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 151)
- Winners Circle Fashions, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 152)
- Winona Knitting Mills, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 153)
- Winport Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 154)
- Wipo, Inc., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 155)
- Wiss, J. & Sons Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 156)
- Witmor, Inc., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 157)
- Wolf & Company, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 158)
- Wolf, Howard B., Inc., 1976 (Box 83, Folder 159)
- Woods, S. E. - Holden, Inc., 1967 (Box 83, Folder 160)
- Woodward & Lothrop, Inc., 1968 (Box 83, Folder 161)
- Woolf Brothers, Inc., 1956 (Box 83, Folder 162)
- Wordley Bedding & Furniture Company, Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 163)
- Work Glove Institute, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 164)
- Work Wear Corp. (Hoover Uniforms, Inc.), 1973 (Box 83, Folder 165)
- Work Wear Corp. (Image Wear), 1975 (Box 83, Folder 166)
- Work Wear Corp. (Industrial Control Systems), 1967 (Box 83, Folder 167)
- Work Wear Corp. (Main Street Fashions, Inc.), 1971 (Box 83, Folder 168)
- Work Wear Corp. (Mars Manufacturing Company), 1969 (Box 83, Folder 169)
- World Discount Department Stores, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 170)
- World Wide, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 171)
- Worsted-Tex, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 172)
- Wrangler Western Wear, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 173)
- Wright, Spencer, Industries, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 174)
- Wyner, R. H. Associates, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 175)
- Xantex Knits, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 176)
- XCEL Corp. Belvidere, NJ (Subsidiary Polymer Materials, Inc.), 1978 (Box 83, Folder 177)
- XCEL Corp. Newark, NJ (Subsidiary Polymer Materials, Inc.), 1979 (Box 83, Folder 178)
- XEROX of Canada, Ltd., 1973 (Box 83, Folder 179)
- X-TYAL International Corporation, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 180)
- Yarn Carriers, Inc., 1972 (Box 83, Folder 181)
- Yarntex Corp., 1973 (Box 83, Folder 182)
- Yates Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1970 (Box 83, Folder 183)
- York Heel, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 184)
- Young, Diane, Sportswear, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 185)
- Zeller Formals, Inc., 1971 (Box 83, Folder 186)
- Zenith Plastics, Inc., 1970 (Box 83, Folder 187)
- Zielinski, Michael A. Co., 1965 (Box 83, Folder 188)
- Zimmerli Underwear of Switzerland, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 189)
- Zittenfield Products, Inc., 1978 (Box 83, Folder 190)
- A & A Manufacturing Co., 1972-1981 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  Division of Chief Apparel
- A & H Sportswear Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- A & S Novelty Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- ATC Casuals, Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- ADG Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- ATO Inc. [Folder 1 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  Annual Reports
- ATO Inc. [Folder 2 of 2], 1977-1980 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- ATP Processors Ltd., 1977-1982 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  Includes Newspaper Clippings
- A.V.V.C. Tre, Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  Importer of mens sweaters
- Abbeville Shirt Makers, Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Abels For Boys, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Abex Corporation, 1970-1981 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Above The Belt, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  Newspaper Clipping
- ACME Children's Wear, Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Acme Tops, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Action Apparel, Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Active Apparel, Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Adams Boot Company, Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Adell Corp., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Adell Plastics Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Advance Transformer, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Advertising Distributors of America of W. PA., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Aero Drapery Co., 1968-1983 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  See also Minnesota Fabrics, Inc., includes newspaper clippings
- Aetna Shirt Corporation, 1966-1983 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  Includes newspaper Clippings
- Agache [Folder 1 of 2], 1964-1981 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  Korvettes, Inc.
- Agache [Folder 2 of 2], 1964-1981 (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Aileen, Inc., 1975-1983 (Box 84, Folder 27)
- Alagold Corporation, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 28)
- Alamo Manufacturing Co., 1981-1983 (Box 84, Folder 29)
- Albain Shirt Co., Inc., 1963-1982 (Box 84, Folder 30)
- Alben Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  Chicago, IL
- Alden's Inc., 1961-1973 (Box 84, Folder 32)
- Alden Shoe Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 33)
- Algy Shoes, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 34)
- All State Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 35)
- Allegheny Label, Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 36)
- Allegheny Shirt Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 37)
- Allegro, Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 38)
  Newspaper clipping
- Allen Industries, Inc., 1967-1983 (Box 84, Folder 39)
- Allen Overall Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 40)
- Allen Shoe Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 41)
- Alpha Richard Corporation, 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 42)
  Newspaper Clipping Included
- Alpha Sierra, Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 43)
- Alrose Shoe Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 44)
- Amarex, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 45)
  Newspaper article photocopy
- American Cotton Yarns, Inc., 1972-1982 (Box 84, Folder 46)
  Newspaper Clippings included
- American Feather Products Corporation, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 47)
- American Flange & Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 48)
  Carol Stream, IL; Linden, NJ
- American Headwear Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 49)
  Allentown, PA
- American Institutional Textile Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 50)
- American Manufacturing Company Inc. [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1983 (Box 84, Folder 51)
- American Manufacturing Company Inc. [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1983 (Box 84, Folder 52)
- American Olean Tile Co., 1978-1981 (Box 84, Folder 53)
  Subsidiary Of National Gypsum Co., Cloverport and Lewisport KY
- American Sanitary Wiping Cloth Company, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 54)
  Paterson, NJ
- American Technical Industries, Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 55)
  American Tree & Wreath Co., Subsidiary
- Ampco-Pittsburgh Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 56)
- Ampro, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 57)
- Amsted Industries, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 58)
  Plexco, Subsidiary; Knoxville, TN
- Amtex, Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 59)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy Included
- Anchor Brush Co., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 60)
  Subsidiary Of North American Philips Corp.; Aurora, IL
- An-Cor Industrial Plastic, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 84, Folder 61)
  Buffalo, NY
- Andlinger & Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 62)
- Andrews Glass Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 63)
  Subsidiary Of Fischer & Porter Co.
- Androme Leather, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 84, Folder 64)
- Animal Protective Foundation of Schenectady, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 65)
- Anwelt Corporation, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 66)
- Appalachian Tire Products Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 67)
- Apparelcraft, Inc., 1962-1981 (Box 84, Folder 68)
- I. Appel Corporation, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 69)
- Appliance Industries, Inc., 1976-1983 (Box 84, Folder 70)
  Subsidiary Welbilt, Inc.; Freeland, PA
- Ararat Knits, Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 71)
- Ar-Bil Manufacturing Corporation, Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 72)
- Arcata National Corporation, 1969-1980 (Box 84, Folder 73)
  Menlo Park, CA
- Arcata Microfilm Corporation, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 74)
  Subsidiary Of Arcata Corp.
- Aries Group, Ltd., 1975-1983 (Box 84, Folder 75)
- Arkay Packaging Corporation, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 76)
- Arlan's Department Stores, Inc., 1971-1980 (Box 84, Folder 77)
  Newspaper Clippings Included
- Arlen Realty & Development Corp. [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1982 (Box 84, Folder 78)
- Arlen Realty & Development Corp. [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1982 (Box 84, Folder 79)
- Arnold Industries, Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 80)
- Arrowhead Enterprises, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 84, Folder 81)
- Asher Association, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 82)
- Ashley Manufacturer, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 83)
- Ashley Quilting Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 84)
- Associated Dry Goods Corporation, 1972-1982 (Box 84, Folder 85)
- Associated Telephone Design, Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 86)
- Astro Dye Works, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 87)
  Article Photocopy
- Atlas Children's Wear, Inc., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 88)
- Auburn Hosiery Mills, Inc., 1971-1983 (Box 84, Folder 89)
- Augusta Bag & Burlap Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 90)
- Augusta Bedding Co., 1980 (Box 84, Folder 91)
  Subsidiary Of Dixie Bedding Co., Inc.; Augusta GA
- Augustus Fashions Ltd., 1977-1981 (Box 84, Folder 92)
  See also: Canaan Fashions
- Automatic Business Products, Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 93)
- Automatic Data Processing, Inc., 1971-1981 (Box 84, Folder 94)
- Avent Manufacturing Corporation, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 95)
  Richmond, VA
- Avon Glove Corporation, 1968-1983 (Box 84, Folder 96)
  Subsidiary Of Hudson Manufacturing Corp.
- BBG Textile Corporation, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 97)
- BDJ Contracting Corporation, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 98)
  Hoboken, NJ
- B.P. Britches, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 99)
- BTH Tanning, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 100)
- B-W Footwear Co., Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 101)
- Bagcraft Corporation of America, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 102)
- Bago Ltd., Inc., 1981 (Box 84, Folder 103)
- Baldwin Manufacturing Co., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 104)
- Ballet Makers, Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 105)
- Ballston Knitting Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 106)
  Newspaper Clipping and Photocopy
- Bama Mills of New Jersey, Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 107)
- Bancroft Sporting Goods Co., 1974-1980 (Box 84, Folder 108)
  Woonsocket, RI; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Barbizon Corp., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 109)
- Barwil Industries, Inc., 1982 (Box 84, Folder 110)
- Barnes, Jhane Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 111)
- D.J. Barnes Lumber Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 84, Folder 112)
- Barnstable Bus Co., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  Barnstable, MA
- Baronova, Ltd., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- William Barry, Inc., 1957-1983 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  See also: Shutzer Industries, Inc.
- Barth-Spencer Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Bart-Kay Novelty Corporation, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Bartolini, Enrico Designs, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- E.T. Barwick Industries, Inc., 1970-1983 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- E.T. Barwick Industries, Inc. Annual Reports [Folder 1 of 2], 1968-1981 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- E.T. Barwick Industries, Inc. Annual Reports [Folder 2 of 2], 1968-1981 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Basic Item, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Bath Industries, Inc., 1966-1978 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  See also: PRF Corporation
- Baxter Rubber Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Bay State Mills, Inc., 1974-1982 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  Holyoke, MA
- Bayeux Fabrics, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Beal's Linen Service, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Beau Brummel Ties, Inc., 1957-1982 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Beaunit Fabrics Corporation, 1978-1981 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Beaver Dam Industries, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Beavertown Weaving Mills, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Becker Bag Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Beckman Instruments, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Bedford Weaving Company, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- Bee Chemical Co., 1973-1982 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  Fairfield and Union City, NJ
- Beldoch Industries Corporation, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Bell Molded Products Corporation, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- Belle Neckwear Co., Inc., 1967-1981 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy
- Belmont Garment Co., 1965-1982 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Belmont Yarn Corporation, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 28)
- Belson Uniform Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- Be-Mine Playwear Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 30)
- Benchmark Industries, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 31)
- Bendinger Bros. Inc., 1966-1983 (Box 85, Folder 32)
- Benedetto, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 33)
- Benson Mailing & Shipping Service, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 34)
- Benson Shoe Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 35)
- Bentex Kiddie Corporation, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 36)
- Bentley Carpet Mills, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 37)
- Berenson Pari-Mutual of New Hampshire, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 38)
  Belmont, NH
- Berkshire Tanning Corporation, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 39)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; North Adams, MA
- Bernat Yarn & Craft Corporation, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 40)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy; Uxbridge, MA
- Bernie Shoe Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 41)
- Bertlyn Industries, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 42)
- Berven Carpets Corporation, 1969-1983 (Box 85, Folder 43)
- Berven Carpets Corporation. Annual Reports [Folder 1 of 2], 1974-1980 (Box 85, Folder 44)
- Berven Carpets Corporation. Annual Reports [Folder 2 of 2], 1974-1980 (Box 85, Folder 45)
- Bess Fabrics Co., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 46)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy; Paterson, NJ
- George Besson, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 47)
  Newspaper Clipping; Merged with DeBucci Designs
- Best Manufacturing Corporation, 1967-1982 (Box 85, Folder 48)
- Betten Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 49)
- Bilray Manufacturing, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 50)
- Bil-Vi Manufacturing Co., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 51)
- Bimba Manufacturing Co., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 52)
- Binney & Smith, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 53)
- Bixby International Corporation, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 54)
- Blackburn Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1972-1981 (Box 85, Folder 55)
- J.S. Blank & Co., 1967-1982 (Box 85, Folder 56)
- Blau Sport-Mates Corporation, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 57)
- Bloomsburg Carpet Industries, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 58)
- Blue Ridge Woven Label Co., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 59)
  Subsidiary Warner Artex
- Bodin Apparel, Inc., 1973-1980 (Box 85, Folder 60)
- Bond Cote of Virginia, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 61)
- Bonders, Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 62)
- Bon-Ten Contracting Corporation, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 63)
- Bonus Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 64)
- Boulangerie Beausejour Et Freres, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 65)
  Acton Vale, Quebec, Canada
- Bourne-Film Music, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 66)
- Brackett & Associates, Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 67)
- Bra-Coe Sportswear, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 68)
- Brady Felt Products Co., Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 85, Folder 69)
  Pittsburgh, PA
- Brass Uniforms, Inc., 1972-1981 (Box 85, Folder 70)
- Braten Apparel Corporation, 1968-1982 (Box 85, Folder 71)
  Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies
- Brecon Knitting Mill, Inc., 1982 (Box 85, Folder 72)
- J. Breed Clothing, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 73)
- Breneman, Inc., 1973-1980 (Box 85, Folder 74)
  Oswego, NY
- Brentwood Clothes, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 75)
- Brentwood Sportswear, Inc., 1968-1981 (Box 85, Folder 76)
- Brierwood Shoe Factory, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 77)
- Bright-Crest Ltd., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 78)
- Broadway Clothing Corporation, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 79)
- George Brockman & Co., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 80)
- Brook Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1961-1982 (Box 85, Folder 81)
- Brookfield Clothes, Inc., 1975-1983 (Box 85, Folder 82)
- Brookline Fabrics, Inc., 1972-1982 (Box 85, Folder 83)
- David Brooks Ltd., Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 84)
- Brooks & Perkins, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 85)
- Bruce Plastics, Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 86)
- Brunswick Outerwear Corporation, 1975-1983 (Box 85, Folder 87)
- Bruxton Shirt Co., 1970-1982 (Box 85, Folder 88)
  Newspaper Clippings
- Buckeye Industries, Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 89)
- Bunn Shoe Co., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 90)
  Humboldt, TN
- Burg, A.S. & Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 91)
  Salem, MA
- Burnham-Edina Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 85, Folder 92)
- Burton-Dixie Corporation, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 93)
- CAM Corporation, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 94)
- C.B. Textiles Corporation, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 95)
- CBS Imports Corporation, 1969-1979 (Box 85, Folder 96)
- C-D Sportswear, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 97)
- CIM Corporation, 1976-1982 (Box 85, Folder 98)
- CN Associates, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 99)
- CPL Corporation, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 100)
  E. Providence, RI
- CSI Industries, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 101)
- C-Tek Installation Services, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 102)
- Cabot Corporation, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 103)
  Subsidiary Of E-A-R Corporation
- Cal-Art Sportswear, Inc., 1983 (Box 85, Folder 104)
  Pamphlet
- Calabria Imports Ltd., Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 105)
- Caladon Industries, 1973-1981 (Box 85, Folder 106)
  City of Industry, CA
- Calford Company, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 107)
- California Flower Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 108)
- Cambridge Rubber Co., 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 109)
- Cameo, Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 110)
- D. Camerato Designs for Executive Suite, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 111)
- Campo Slacks, Inc., 1963-1980 (Box 85, Folder 112)
  Houtzdale, PA; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Can-Pac, Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 113)
- Candur Plastics Ltd., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 114)
- Canton Textile Mills. General, 1971-1981 (Box 85, Folder 115)
- Caper Mates Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 116)
  Subsidiary Of Famous Cottons Inc.
- United States Shoe Corporation, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 117)
  Capezio Wholesale Shoes, Division
- Caprice Footwear, Inc., 1980 (Box 85, Folder 118)
- Carbon Hill Manufacturing Corporation, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 119)
  New York Pants
- Cardinal Blouse Inc., 1981 (Box 85, Folder 120)
- Caress of California, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 121)
  Los Angeles, CA
- Caresse Clothing, Inc., 1980 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Carleton Place Textile Ltd., 1981 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Carnation Company. Annual Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Carnival Bag Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  Brooklyn, NY
- Carolina Eastman Co., 1970 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Carter Service Industries, Inc., 1983 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Catawba Sox, Inc., 1980 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Catchit Sportswear, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Cavnar-Johnson Cordage Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Century III Electronics International, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Chamberlin Rubber Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Charisma Fashions, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Charlton Woolen Co., 1970-1981 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; Charlton City, MA
- Chelsea Industries, Inc., 1971-1982 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; Emerson Textiles, Inc.; Chelsea, MA
- Chelsea Industries, Inc., 1973-1978 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; Futura Fabrics Corporation; W. Hazelton, PA
- Chelsea Industries, Inc., 1967-1979 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy; Tectra Industries/Weaving Corporation of America; W. Warwick, RI
- Chemcut Corporation, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Chemionics Corporation, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- Cherokee Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1971-1983 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- Chesa International Ltd., 1971-1982 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Chesterfield Manufacturing Corporation, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Chesterfield Webbing Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  Newspaper Clipping; Chesterfield, SC
- Chestnut Fleet Rentals, Inc., 1980 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- Chevron Chemical Co., 1973-1982 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  Newspaper Clippings Included; Polymer Division; Dayton, TN
- Chic Hosiery Corporation, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  Newspaper Clipping; Charlotte, NC
- Christiansburg Garment Co., Inc., 1978-1982 (Box 86, Folder 26)
- Cilco, Inc., 1982 (Box 86, Folder 27)
- Cindarn Plastics Inc., 1983 (Box 86, Folder 28)
- Cisco Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included
- Clark Copy International Corporation, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 30)
- Cleaners Hanger Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 86, Folder 31)
- Clemco Products Inc., 1983 (Box 86, Folder 32)